United University Professions (UUP); Records apap039
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of the President, 1971-1997; III; 35.20 cubic ft.
  - Projects/Subjects -- Samuel Wakshull, 1971-May 1981; 3; 7.0 cubic ft.
    - Subject Files [RESTRICTED], 1971-May 1981; 1975-May 1981; 3.1; 5.33 cubic ft.
      - *Leadership Bulletins for chapter leadership [RESTRICTED], January 1978-July 1979 (Box III.3.3 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - Legal Opinions-Miscellaneous and UUP specific [RESTRICTED], 1974-1980; 3 folders (Box III.3.3 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35-37)
      - Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1977-1981 (Box III.3.3 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
      - *Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box III.3.3 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
      - *Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box III.3.3 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
      - *Legislative Days 1977 [RESTRICTED], February-June 1977 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Legislative Day [RESTRICTED], March 1978 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - *Levittown Decision, The Evidence and the Conclusions (NYSUT report) [RESTRICTED], April 1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Librarians [Academic Status] and UUP Task Force on Librarians' Concerns [RESTRICTED], October 1974-December 1975 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Librarians [Academic Status] [RESTRICTED], May 1977-June 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - *Life Insurance mailing to bargaining unit members [RESTRICTED], January 1978 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - *Lobbyist Statement of Registration-UUP [RESTRICTED], March 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - McGrath, Thomas (Grievance) [RESTRICTED], December 1974; September 1976-December 1976 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - Managerial/Confidential [RESTRICTED], October 1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - Membership-Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - Membership-Insurance, benefits, and other [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - *Milton, John-public relations consultant [RESTRICTED], July 1980-July 1981 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence [RESTRICTED], April 1975-May 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous [Wakshull personal correspondence?] [RESTRICTED], 1970s (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - *NEA [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16-17)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Albany Student Press [RESTRICTED], September-October 1978 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Charles Baker [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], October 1977-October 1978 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
      - *NEA/NYEA Challenge-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], December 1978 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
      - *NEA/NYEA-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1975-March 1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
      - *NEA/NYEA and SUNY Alliance [RESTRICTED], October 1977-February 1981 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
      - Negotiations Bulletins [RESTRICTED], October 1975-November 1976 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
      - Negotiations-Proposals, Committee, Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
      - Negotiations-Reopened [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
      - New Rank for Academics [RESTRICTED], October 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
      - New York Educators Association (NYEA) [RESTRICTED], February 1979-November 1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], April 1975-March 1976 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], April 1976-February 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
      - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT)-Board of Directors [RESTRICTED], September 1976-October 1977 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
      - Newsletter-"From the President's Log" [RESTRICTED], February 1976-June 1976 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
      - Newspaper clippings [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
      - Non-Teaching Professionals (NTP) [RESTRICTED], 1976; 1978; 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Counsel [RESTRICTED], November 1976-October 1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35A)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Frucher, Meyer (Director) [RESTRICTED], January 1979-September 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Hartnett, Thomas (Deputy Director) [RESTRICTED], November 1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Hodes, Nancy (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], July 1979-May 1980 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Kershaw, Leonard (Assistant Director) [RESTRICTED], July 1977-December 1978 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Northrop, James (Deputy Director) [RESTRICTED], September 1978-May 1979 (Box III.3.4 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
      - Office of Employee Relations, NYS (OER)-Wollett, Donald (Director) [RESTRICTED], October 1975-October 1978 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - OMB Circular A-21-Cost principles for educational institutions/personnel activity reporting system [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - *Our State-NYSUT newsletter (saved for NEA coverage?) [RESTRICTED], October 1976-March 1978 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - *Parking [RESTRICTED], May 1978-September 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Patent Policy (SUNY) and UUP Patent Waiver Policy Committee [RESTRICTED], November 1975-April 1977; April 1979-October 1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Potsdam-National Center for Higher Education Management Systems survey/reorganization job descriptions [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Powell, Elwin (SUNY Buffalo) (academic freedom) [RESTRICTED], September 1976-February 1977 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Project for Adult College Education (PACE) [RESTRICTED], October 1978-February 1981 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - Public Employees Federation (PEF) [RESTRICTED], July 1978-November 1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - Reform Caucus [RESTRICTED], October 5, 1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], March 1976-December 1977 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], January 1979-June 1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], August 1979-January 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
      - Regents (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], February 1980-August 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - Representative Assembly (NYSUT) [RESTRICTED], December 1976-March 1977 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
      - Research (miscellaneous? student/faculty ratios, workload, ranks) [RESTRICTED], December 1977-April 1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
      - Research Foundation (SUNY) [RESTRICTED], January 1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
      - Retraining Program/Retraining Committee [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
      - Retrenchments [RESTRICTED], June 1975-May 1977; November 1979; March 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
      - *Right to Work [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
      - Salary Issues [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
      - Save SUNY day/SUNY budget cut opposition [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22-23)
      - *Senate Professional Association (SPA) [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
      - Senates (campus) [RESTRICTED], July 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
      - *Sentry Insurance-Catastrophic Medical Coverage Plan [RESTRICTED], June-July 1978 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
      - Staff (NYSUT field staff and UUP admin. office) [RESTRICTED], 1975-May 1978 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
      - Staff (NYSUT field staff and UUP admin. office) [RESTRICTED], June 1978-November 1979; December 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
      - *State University Professional Association [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
      - Statewide Coalition for Public Higher Education [RESTRICTED], December 1980-February 1981 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
      - Student Association of the State University of New York (SASU) [RESTRICTED], January 1979-December 1980 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
      - *SUNY and Governor's Office of Employee Relations-Miscellaneous (folder 1 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
      - *SUNY and Governor's Office of Employee Relations-Miscellaneous (folder 2 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
      - *SUNY and Governor's Office of Employee Relations-Miscellaneous (folder 3 of 3) [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - *SUNY Budget/UUP Budget 1978-79 [RESTRICTED], January-November 1978 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - *SUNY Budget 1979-80 [RESTRICTED], February-December 1979 (Box III.3.5 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - *SUNY Budget 1980-81 (folder 1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], December 1979-June 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - *SUNY Budget 1980-81 (folder 2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], October 1979-February 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - SUNY-CUNY Merger/Wessell Commission [Temporary State Commission on the Future of Post-Secondary Education] [RESTRICTED], January-April 1977; July-September 1978 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - SUNY Day Care Centers [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - SUNY Policy-Award of Academic Credit by Examination [RESTRICTED], July-August 1976 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - TIAA-CREF (Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association/College Retirement Equity Fund) [RESTRICTED], 1979; 1981 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Unity Caucus [RESTRICTED], June 1976-April 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Universitas (newsletter-University Professors for Academic Order) [RESTRICTED], October 1978-June 1979 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - *Update-newsletter for local leaders of NYSUT [RESTRICTED], April 1976-June 1978 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - UUP Budget [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - *UUP Office [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976; 1982 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - UUP Project Expenses/Budget [RESTRICTED], September 1977-December 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - VOTE/COPE [RESTRICTED], March 1978-April 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
      - *Wakshull article-Labor Law Journal (NEA related) [RESTRICTED], March 1978 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - Workload [RESTRICTED], September 1976-October 1976 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
      - *Zelden, Marvin (Editor, universitas) [RESTRICTED], July-September 1978; August-September 1979 (Box III.3.6 (3.1-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Administrative Files [RESTRICTED], 1971-April 1981; 1975-April 1981; 3.2; 1.67 cubic ft.
      Incoming and outgoing correspondence from UUP's President, Executive Director, and other UUP personnel; as well as internal correspondence between the President, Executive Director, membership coordinator, and NYSUT legal counsel. Materials were filed by chapter involved, under individual name (relating to grievance matters, and also for UUP personnel matters), and occasionally by subject. Topics covered include retrenchments on campuses; appointments to and resignations from committees; campus specific concerns; grievances; questions from members regarding benefits and membership; resolutions sent in by chapters; minutes for chapter board meetings as well as chapter labor/management meetings; and information on chapter officers. The amount and type of information available for each chapter varies widely. Additional records on individual chapters make up Subseries 3.3 in Subgroup IV, Office of the Secretary. Agency fee issues and the separation of UUP from NEA are infrequent topics of discussion. The records for the Grievance Committee in this series include reports to the President presenting the committee's position on/view of the grievances under its consideration. These reports provide some of the most detailed information available regarding the issues that UUP has sought to remedy through grievances on behalf of its bargaining unit members.
      One recurring concern reflected in the President's correspondence with chapter leaders is the reasons behind the resignation of UUP members, particularly as UUP was seeking during this period to shore up its membership not only to defeat the NEA/NYEA and other challengers, but to provide the strongest front possible for future contract negotiations. Although the bulk of the materials in this series cover the Wakshull administration (1975-1981), this series also includes some documents from the DeLucia administration (1973-1975).
      - Albany Chapter [RESTRICTED], September 1974-November 1975 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
      - Albany Chapter [RESTRICTED], January 1977-January 1981 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
      - Alfred Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-February 1978 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
      - Binghamton Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-June 1979 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-May 1976 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], June 1976-August 1977 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], September 1977-July 1978 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
      - Brockport Chapter [RESTRICTED], August 1978-October 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
      - Buffalo Center Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1975-August 1977 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
      - Buffalo Center Chapter [RESTRICTED], September 1977-February 1981 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
      - Buffalo Health Science Center Chapter [RESTRICTED], October 1975-October 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
      - Buffalo State University College Chapter [RESTRICTED], August 1975-December 1975 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
      - Buffalo State University College Chapter [RESTRICTED], January 1976-October 1977 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
      - Buffalo State University College Chapter [RESTRICTED], November 1977-September 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
      - Canton Chapter [RESTRICTED], December 1974-April 1980 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
      - Carey, Hugh (NYS Governor) and Office of Employee Relations [RESTRICTED], November 1975-August 1977 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
      - Central Administration Chapter [RESTRICTED], July 1975-October 1978 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
      - Certification Program in Teacher Education/Commissioner's Task Force on Teacher Education and Certification [CBTE] [RESTRICTED], October 1974-April 1976 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - Chapter Leadership Directory [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - Chapter Presidents [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1976 (Box III.3.6 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - Chapter Presidents [RESTRICTED], August 1976-November 1979; September 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Cobleskill Chapter [RESTRICTED], March 1976-November 1978 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (union-wide) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1976 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Cortland Chapter [RESTRICTED], March 1975-February 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - CSEA (Civil Service Employee Association) [RESTRICTED], December 1976-March 1979 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - CUNY (City University of New York) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-July 1977 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Delhi Chapter [RESTRICTED], June 1975-March 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Downstate Medical Center [Brooklyn] Chapter [RESTRICTED], November 1975-February 1978 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - Downstate Medical Center [Brooklyn] Chapter [RESTRICTED], March 1978-April 1981 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - Empire State College Chapter [RESTRICTED], August 1975-February 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - Environmental Science and Forestry Chapter [RESTRICTED], July 1977-August 1978 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - Executive Board [RESTRICTED], May 1975-February 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - Farmingdale Chapter [RESTRICTED], May 1975-December 1977 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
      - Farmingdale Chapter [RESTRICTED], January 1978-March 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - Fredonia Chapter [RESTRICTED], February 1975-March 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
      - Freedom of Information Law (NY) [RESTRICTED], 1974; 1977 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
      - Geneseo Chapter [RESTRICTED], May 1975-October 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
      - Glasheen, Richard (Stony Brook) (grievance) [RESTRICTED], September 1975-August 1977 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
      - Gordon, Murray [counsel re: Health Science Center negotiations] [RESTRICTED], October 1975-July 1976 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
      - Grievance Committee [RESTRICTED], April 1975-August 1977 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
      - Harding, Nicholas J. [statewide Secretary] [RESTRICTED], May 1975 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
      - Health Science Centers (including re: Health Science Center Caucus and Clinical Practice Management Plan) [RESTRICTED], May 1975-September 1975 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
      - Health Science Centers (including re: Health Science Center Caucus and Clinical Practice Management Plan) [RESTRICTED], October 1975-February 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
      - Human Rights, Division of [NYS] [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
      - Legislation-NYSUT [RESTRICTED], May 1979-February 1981 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
      - Legislation (committee, corresp. from legislators, information on legislation) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
      - Legislation (correspondence from legislators, testimony, copies of legislation) [RESTRICTED], November 1975-March 1981 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
      - Long Island Meetings [RESTRICTED], May-December 1975 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
      - March 16 Rally (SUNY budget cuts) [RESTRICTED], February-March 1976 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
      - Maritime Chapter [RESTRICTED], February 1975-March 1978 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
      - Morrisville Chapter [RESTRICTED], September 1975-March 1981 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
      - New Paltz Chapter [RESTRICTED], July 1975-June 1977 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
      - New Paltz Chapter [RESTRICTED], July 1977-March 1979 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
      - New Paltz Chapter [RESTRICTED], April 1979-November 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - Old Westbury Chapter [RESTRICTED], March 1975-November 1980 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - Oneonta Chapter [RESTRICTED], July 1975-October 1979 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - Optometry, College of, Chapter [RESTRICTED], December 1975-May 1979 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
      - Potsdam Chapter-Personnel Data System [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box III.3.7 (3.2-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)